Finding Aid for the Ronald Jacobs Papers PASC.0355
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Joey Bishop Show (The)
  - Joey, Jack Jones and the Genie - script, 1964 Feb 14 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Joey, the Good Samaritan - revised script, 1963 Feb 25 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Joey's Courtship - script, 1964 Oct 15 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    Writers: Stewart, Charles
  - Joey's Dramatic Debut - revised script, 1963 Jan 11 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    Formerly titled Hooray for Hollywood
  - Joey's Hideaway Cabin - script, 1963 Nov 4 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    Writers: Helm, Harvey; Bregman, Paul
  - Joey's Lucky Cuff Links - revised script, 1962 Oct 22 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    Writers: Fox, Fred S.; Elinson, Iz; Freeman, Fred; Marshall, Garry
  - Joey's Moustache - script, 1963 Mar 17 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Joey's Replacement - script, 1962 Aug 2 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Joey's Surprise for Ellie (Or: Ellie Flips Her Wig) - script, 1963 Sep 3 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    Writers: Goodman, Ralph; Dreben, Stan
  - Joey's Twilight Zone - script, 1963 Mar 25 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Masquerade Party (The) - script, 1963 Feb 1 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - My Son, the Doctor - script, 1963 Mar 5 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Nielsen Box (The) - revised script, 1964 Jul 20 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Penguins Three - script, 1962 Jul 5 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    Writers: Freeman, Fred; Marshall, Garry
  - Perfect Girl (The) - script, 1964 Oct 1 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Rusty Arrives - script, 1964 Nov 5 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Rusty's Education - revised script, 1964 Nov 12 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Something of Value - revised script, 1963 Aug 12 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Something of Value - script, 1963 Jul 1 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Sultan's Gift (The) - revised script, 1964 Dec 10 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Three's a Crowd - revised script, 1962 Jul 23 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Two Little Maids Are We - script, 1963 Sep 23 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Weed City Story (The) - revised script, 1964 Nov 18 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Weekend in the Mountains - revised script, 1963 Dec 9 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Weekend in the Mountains - script, 1963 Nov 8 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - What'll You Have? - revised script, 1964 Dec 18 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - You're What? Again? - script, 1964 Sep 9 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Zsa Zsa Redecorates the Nursery - script, 1963 Nov 18 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Zsa Zsa Redecorates the Nursery - script, 1963 Nov 9 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    Writers: Fox, Fred; Elinson, Iz
- Make Room for Granddaddy
  - Arrangement (The) - revised script, 1970 Aug 25 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    Writers: Kwai, Tawasaki; Mitsubi, Samuro
  - Big Hang-Up (The) - script, 1970 Mar 26 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    Writers: Shaw, Lou
  - Fangs for the Memory - script, 1970 Apr 3 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    Writers: Erwin, Lee
  - Greatest Ear in the Business (The) - script, 1971 Jan 12 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Hamburger for a Frank (A) - revised script, 1970 Sep 24 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    Writers: Kahn, Bernie
  - He Did It His Way - revised script, 1970 Jul 21 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    Writers: Garson, Hank
  - Horrible Horoscope (The) - revised script, 1970 Jul 14 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Is This Trip Necessary? - script, 1970 Sep 22 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Karate Kate - script, 1970 Oct 5 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    Writers: Long, S.A.
  - Make Room for Grandson - revised script, 1970 Jun 16 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Matter of Principle (A) - revised script, 1970 Aug 8 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Of Mice and Mini - revised script, 1970 Sep 15 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Over Thirty is Out - script, 1970 Nov 3 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    Writers: Monaster, Nate
  - Teaching Linda to Drive - revised script, 1970 May 20 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    Writers: Bonaduce, Joseph; Bonaduce, Betty
  - Teen Idol (The) - revised script, 1970 Sep 1 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - This Granddaddy Rated X - revised script, 1970 Sep 3 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Will the Real Diana Please Stand Up - script, 1970 Nov 3 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    Writers: Adler, D.
- Mayberry R.F.D.
  - Aloha, Goober - script, 1969 Dec 29 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Caper (The) - script, 1969 Sep 2 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Emmett and the Ring - script, 1969 Nov 12 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Emmett Takes a Fall - script, 1969 Oct 13 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    Writers: Mosher, Bob
  - Farmer Exchange Project (The) - script, 1969 Aug 7 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    Writers: Whitcomb, Dennis; West, Paul
  - Goober's Niece - script, no date (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Health Fun (The) - script, 1969 Dec 3 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    Writers: Swanson, Joel; Mosher, Bob
  - Mayberry Float (The) - script, 1969 Nov 19 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    Writers: West, Paul
  - Mayberry Road (The) - script, 1969 Nov 5 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Mike's Birthday Party - script, 1969 Jul 17 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Millie and the Great Outdoors - script, 1970 Jan 7 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Millie and the Palm Springs Golf Pro - script, 1969 Sep 16 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Millie the Secretary - script, 1969 Jul 30 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Mynah Bed (The) - script, 1969 Oct 21 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - New Farm Hand (The) - script, 1969 Aug 14 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - New Well (The) - script, 1969 Nov 25 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    Writers: Swanson, Joel; Grant, Perry; Bensfield, Dick
  - Palm Springs Cowboy - script, 1969 Sep 19 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Palm Springs Here We Are - script, 1969 Sep 16 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Palm Springs Here We Come - script, 1969 Aug 29 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Sculptor (The) - script, 1969 Dec 10 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Mod Squad (The)
  - Activist (The) - revised script, 1970 Aug 17 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    Writers: Rubin, Mann
  - Assignment: Synanon - script, 1969 Dec 10 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    Writers: Bennett, Harve
  - Bad Man on Campus - script, 1968 Jun 17 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    Writers: Heverly, Robert
  - Bummer for R.J. (A) - revised script, 1970 Oct 28 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    Writers: Turley, Jack
  - Call Back Yesterday - revised script, 1970 Jan 22 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    Writers: Young, Robert Malcolm; Bloch, John W.
  - Captain Greer Call Surgery - script, 1968 Jul 9 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    Writers: Lawrence, Tony
  - Comeback (The) - revised script, 1971 Jan 7 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Confrontations - script, 1969 Jul 11 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    Writers: Bellak, George
  - Deadly Sin (The) - script, 1969 Dec (Box 42, Folder 8)
    Writers: Young, Robert Malcolm
  - Death of Wild Bill Hannacheck (The) - script, 1969 Aug 22 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    Writers: Saha, Mark
  - Debt (The) - script, 1969 Nov 20 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    Writers: Barrett, Steffi; Barrett, Tony
  - Doing the Thing in Soulsville - script, 1968 Aug 1 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    Writers: Goodwin, Robert L.
  - Double for Danger (A) - revised script, 1970 Nov 11 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    Writers: Lewis, Roger Hill; Bennett, Harve
  - Exile (The) - script, 1969 Nov 28 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    Writers: Richman, Don; Bennett, Harve
  - Eye for an Eye (An) - script, 1969 Jun 3 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Fever - revised script, 1970 Sep 22 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    Writers: Schneider, Margaret; Schneider, Paul
  - Find Tara Chapman - script, 1968 Aug 21 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    Writers: Weingarten, Art; Sanford, Gerald
  - Girl in Chair Nine (The) - revised script, 1969 May 19 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    Writers: Bast, William
  - Guess Who's Coming to Murder - revised script, 1968 Jun 3 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    Writers: Ross, Jeremy
  - Guru (The) - script, 1968 May 6 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    Writers: Chapman, Leigh
  - Healer (The) - script, 1969 Jul 31 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    Writers: Bagni, Gwen; Dubov, Paul
  - Hot Hot Car (The) - revised script, 1970 Nov (Box 43, Folder 6)
    Writers: Schwartz, Elroy
  - In this Corner -- Sol Alpert - script, 1969 Sep 25 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    Writers: Lakin, Rita; Bennet, Harve
  - Is That Justice? No, It's the Law - revised script, 1970 Dec 9 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    Writers: Vowell, David H.
  - Is There Anyone Left in Santa Paula? - revised script, 1970 Oct 15 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    Writers: Coon, Gene L.
  - Judas Trap (The) - revised script, 1970 Oct 2 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    Writers: Black, Walter
  - King of Empty Cups (The) - script, 1969 Oct 28 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    Writers: Roberts, Sonya
  - Lisa - script, 1969 Aug 14 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Loser (The) - script, 1970 Feb 16 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    Writers: Stark, Sheldon
  - Love - script, 1968 Aug 23 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    Writers: Rosenbaum, Henry
  - Mother of Sorrow - script, 1969 Dec 18 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    Writers: Lakin, Rita
  - My Name is Manolete - script, 1969 Jun 10 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    Writers: Armen, Margaret
  - My, What a Pretty Bus - script, 1968 May 28 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Never Give the Fuzz an Even Break - script, 1969 Sep 11 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    Writers: Wald, Marvin
  - Place to Run, A Heart to Hide In (A) - script, 1969 May 19 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Plight Upon the Land (A) - script, 1969 Sep 2 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    Writers: Landau, Richard
  - Price of Terror (The) - script, 1968 Aug 13 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Quiet Weekend in the Country - script, 1968 Sep 9 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    Writers: Gillis, Jackson; Goodwin, Bob
  - Return to Darkness, Return to Light - script, 1970 Jan 18 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Ride the Man Down - revised script, 1969 May 15 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    Writers: Lakso, Edward J.; Bennett, Harve
  - Should Auld Acquaintance Be Forgot - script, 1970 Feb 8 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    Writers: Lakin, Rita; Bennett, Harve
  - Suffer, Little Children - script, 1970 Aug 24 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Sunday Drivers (The) - revised script, 1968 Oct 21 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Survival House - script, 1969 Dec 15 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Sweet Child of Terror - script, 1969 Oct 16 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Teeth of the Barracuda (The) - script, 1967 Oct 24 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Time for Remembering (A) - script, 1970 Jan 12 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Time of Hyacinths (A) - revised script, 1970 Sep 9 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Time to Love -- A Time to Cry (A) - script, 1968 Aug 2 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - To Linc -- With Love - script, 1969 Jul 3 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    Writers: Sobieski, Carol
  - Town Called Sincere (A) - script, 1969 Nov 11 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Up Tight Town (The) - script, 1968 May 13 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    Writers: Katkov, Norman
  - When Smitty Comes Marching Home - script, 1968 Jul 15 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    Writers: Barrett, Tony; Bennett, Harve
- My World and Welcome to It
  - Child's Play - script, 1970 Jan 25 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    Writers: Kleinschmitt, Carl
  - Christabel - script, 1969 Jun 24 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    Writers: Shavelson, Mel
  - Darn that Dream - revised script, 1969 Nov 9 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    Writers: Garrett, Lila; Kahn, Bernie
  - 'Dear' is a Four-Letter Word - revised script, 1969 Nov 13 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    Writers: Tarloff, Erik; Adler, David
  - Disenchanted (The) - script, 1969 May 22 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    Writers: Flippen, Ruth Brooks
  - Figgerin' of Aunt Wilma (The) - script, 1969 Dec 10 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    Writers: Rosen, Milt
  - Fourth Estate (The) - script, 1970 Jan 11 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Friend of the Earth (A) - revised script, 1969 Aug 27 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Ghost and Mr. Monroe (The) - script, 1969 Jun 18 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Human Being and the Dinosaurs (The) - revised script, 1969 Oct 14 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Little Girls are Sugar and Spice - And Not Always Nice - script, 1969 May 15 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Maid in Connecticut - script, 1969 Oct 2 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    Writers: Koch, Tom
  - Mating Dance (The) (We'll Cross That Bridge When We Come to It) - revised script, 1969 Nov 3 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Mea-Culpa Bit (The) - script, 1969 Dec 29 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    Writers: Manhoff, Bill
  - Middle Years (The) - script, 1969 Nov 20 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    Writers: Arnold, Danny; Flippen, Ruth Brooks
  - Monroe the Misogynist - script, 1970 Jan 13 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    Writers: Cutler, Stan; Donovan, Martin
  - Native Wit - script, 1969 Sep 19 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Night the House Caught on Fire (The) - script, 1969 May 16 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    Writers: Shavelson, Melville
  - Nobody Ever Kills Dragons Anymore - revised script, 1969 Aug 21 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    Writers: Sharp, Phil
  - Pilot Script, 1968 Oct 18 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Rally 'Round the Flag - revised script, 1969 Sep 25 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Rules for a Happy Marriage - revised script, 1969 Dec 21 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Saga of Dimity Ann - revised script, 1969 Aug 14 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Seal in the Bedroom - script, 1969 Jun 6 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    Writers: Paul Wayne
  - Shrike and the Chipmunks (The) - script, 1969 Jul 30 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - War Between Men and Women - revised script, 1969 Sep 4 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Wooing of Mr. Monroe - revised script, 1969 Nov 24 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- New People (The)
  - Backlash - script, 1969 Oct 6 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Bartered Bride (In Two Parts) - script, 1969 Sep 8 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    Writers: Gast, Harold
  - Comes the Revolution We use the Girls' Shower - script, 1969 Jul 23 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    Writers: Kirgo, George
  - Fear - script, 1969 Sep 4 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Is This Any Way to Run an Island? - script, 1969 Jun 2 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Writers: Kean, E. Arthur
  - Lifeline - script, 1969 Jun 28 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    Writers: Bloch, John W.
  - Marriage -- Bomano Style - script, 1969 Aug 21 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Murderer - script, 1969 Jul 10 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Of Clay and Wattles Made - revised script, 1969 Oct 23 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - On the Horizon - revised script, 1969 Oct 16 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Panic in the Sand - script, 1969 Jul 21 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Pied Piper of Pot (The) - script, 1969 Jun 18 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Writers: Blum, Edwin
  - Pilot Script, 1968 Nov 27 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    Writers: Serling, Rod
  - Prisoner (The) - revised script, 1969 Sep 29 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    Writers: Kean, E. Arthur; Terpiloff, Anthony
  - Strike Not In Anger - script, 1969 May 27 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Tin God (The) - script, 1969 Jul 9 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Writers: McDaniel, Charles A.
- That Girl
  - 7 1/4 - part two script, 1968 Jul 19 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    This episode may be related to Marlo Thomas the Prattass Special, part one.
    Writers: Julian, Arthur; Flippen, Ruth Brooks; Arnold, Danny
  - All About Ann - revised script, 1966 Sep 30 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Writers: Pascal, Milton
  - All's Well that Ends… - script, 1970 Jan 24 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Writers: Zelinka, Sydney
  - Among My Souvenirs - revised script, 1966 Oct 24 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Writers: Elliott, Peggy; Scharlach, Edmund
  - Anatomy of a Blunder (The) - revised script, 1966 Jul 8 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Writers: McRaven; Kleinschmitt
  - Ann of the Thousand Hiccups - script, 1970 Apr 8 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    Writers: Robinson, Leroy
  - Ann Versus Secretary - script, 1968 Sep 19 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Annie Get Your Gunn - script, 1966 Aug 24 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Writers: Abrams, Gary
  - Apartment (The) - script, 1967 Aug 9 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - At the Drop of a Budget - script, 1969 Jun 20 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Author! Author! - revised script, 1967 Feb 10 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Writers: Axe, Ronald; Harris, Howard
  - Bad Day at Marvin Gardens - script, 1969 Jan 8 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Bet (The) - script, 1970 Jun 3 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Beware of Actors Bearing Gifts - revised script, 1966 Sep 3 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Break A Leg - revised script, 1966 Jun 17 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Writers: Parker, Jim; Margolin, Arnold
  - Chef's Night Out - revised script, 1970 May 22 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Writers: Grossman, Bud
  - Christmas and the Hard Luck Kid - revised script, 1966 Nov 4 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Writers: Brooke, Jim
  - Counter Proposal - revised script, 1970 Apr 17 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    Formerly titled Will You Marry Me?
  - Crime Doesn't Pay????? - script, 1970 Sep 21 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    Formerly known as both Annie the Heister and That Chocolate.
    Writers: Horwitt, Arnold
  - Dark on Top of Everything Else - script, 1968 Sep 13 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Writers: Kleinschmitt, Carl; Flippen, Ruth Brooks; Arnold, Danny
  - Decision Before Dawn - script, 1968 Jul 24 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Writers: Kragen, Jinx; Flippen, Ruth Brooks; Arnold, Danny
  - Defiant One (The) - script, 1968 Dec 12 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    Writers: Baer, Richard; Arnold, Danny
  - Dog for a Day - script, 1966 Jun 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Don and Sandi and Harry and Snoopy - revised script, 1970 May 1 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Formerly titled But Would You Want One to Marry Your Sister.
    Writers: Elliott, Peggy
  - Don't Just Do Something, Stand There - revised script, 1966 Jul 14 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Earrings (The) - script, 1968 Nov 16 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    Writers: Leeds, Howard; Flippen, Ruth Brooks; Arnold, Danny
  - Easy Faller - script, 1970 Jan 24 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Eleven Angry Men and That Girl - script, 1968 Jun 10 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Eye of the Beholder, (The) - script, 1968 Oct 9 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Writers: Wayne, Paul; Arnold, Danny; Flippen, Ruth Brooks
  - Face in the Shower Room Door (The) - script, 1968 Jul 2 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Writers: Cutler, Stan; Donovan, Martin; Idelson, Bill; Flippen, Ruth Brooks
  - Fix My Screen and Bug Out - revised script, 1969 Aug 15 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Flour Child (The) - script, 1969 Jun 10 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    Writers: Pritzker, Steve
  - Fly By Night - scripts for parts one and two, 1969 Nov 18 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Fly Me to the Moon - script, 1968 Nov 26 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Writers: McGreevey, John; Flippen, Ruth Brooks; Arnold, Danny
  - Gone A Courtin' - revised script, 1969 Dec 8 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Gone with the Breeze - script, 1966 Nov 18 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Writers: August, Tom; August, Helen
  - Goodbye, Hello, Goodbye - revised script, 1966 Jul 22 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - H. W. and the W. W. (The) (The Home Wrecker and the Window Washer) - script, 1968 Oct 4 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Hearing Today, Gone Tomorrow - script, 1969 Aug 7 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Help Wanted - revised script, 1966 Aug 26 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Hi-Jack and the Mighty (The) - script, 1968 May 20 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Honeymoon Apartment (The) - revised script, 1967 Jan 27 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Writers: Kalish, Austin; Kalish, Irma
  - I Ain't Got No Body - revised script, 1970 Jun 12 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    Writers: Scharlach, Ed; Murray, Warren S.
  - I Am Curious Lemon - revised script, 1969 Oct 10 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Writers: Barris, Alex
  - I'll Be Suing You - revised script, 1966 Jun 23 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Writers: Elliott; Scharlach
  - It's So Nice to Have a Mouse Around the House - script, 1968 Dec 30 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Writers: Flippen, Ruth Brooks; Arnold, Danny
  - Just Donald and Me and Jerry Makes Three - script, 1968 Aug 14 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Writers: Cutler, Stan; Donovan, Martin; Flippen, Ruth Brooks; Arnold, Danny
  - Kimono My House - revised script, 1966 Dec 9 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Kiss the Girl Goodbye - revised script, 1969 Sep 23 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    Writers: Harris, Fai; Farr, Lynn
  - Leaving the Nest is for the Birds - revised script, 1967 Jan 13 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Writers: Avedon, Barbara
  - Limited Engagement (A) - revised script, 1970 Sep 14 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Little Auction Annie - revised script, 1966 Aug 16 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Many Happy Returns - script, 1968 Nov 8 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Writers: Whedon, John; Flippen, Ruth Brooks; Arnold, Danny
  - Marlo Thomas Prattass Special (The) - part one script, 1968 Jul 10 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    This episode may be related to 7 1/4, part two.
  - Mating Game (The) - revised script, 1967 Feb 17 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Writers: Silverman, Treva; Meyerson, Peter
  - Meet Me in St. Louis (Part One) - script, 1970 Apr 13 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Meet Me in St. Louis (Part Two) - script, 1970 Jul 23 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Meter Maid - revised script, 1969 Oct 1 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Writers: Ross, Jerry; Lynn, William
  - Mission Improbable (Part One) - revised script, 1969 Jul 31 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Mission Improbable (Part Two) - revised script, 1969 Jul 31 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Muggy Day in Central park (A) - script, 1968 Jun 20 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - My Part Belongs to Daddy - revised script, 1969 Jun 14 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - My Sister's Keeper - script, 1968 Sep 19 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Never Change a Diaper on Opening Night - revised scripts (2 copies), 1966 Jul 1 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Formerly titled The Baby Sitter.
  - No Man is Manhattan Island - script, 1970 Apr 20 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Nobody Here But Us Chickens - revised script, 1969 Jun 6 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Nuptial Not (The) - script, 1970 Apr 20 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    Writers: Rainer, Iris; Silver, Susan
  - Opening Night - revised script, 1969 Oct 15 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Paper Hats and Everything (or) A Date With Dad - revised script, 1966 Dec 23 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Writers: Zelinka, Sydney R.
  - Pass the Potatoes, Ethel Merman - script, 1967 Jul 18 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Phantom of the Horse Opera (The) - revised script, 1966 Oct 7 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Philadelphia Story (The) script, 1967 Jun 19 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Pie 'R' Not Square - script, 1968 Oct 31 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    Writers: Rosen, Milt; Flippen, Ruth Brooks; Arnold, Danny
  - Rain, Snow and Rice - revised script, 1966 Dec 16 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Rango the Outlaw - revised script, 1966 Sep 2 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Writers: Singer, Ray
  - Rattle of Simple Gun - revised script, 1970 Apr 25 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Reunion (The) - revised script, 1969 Dec 5 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Rich Little Rich Kid (The) - revised script, 1966 Aug 13 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Russians Are Staying (The) - revised script, 1970 Sep 4 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Secret Ballot - script, 1968 May 20 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Writers: Baer, Richard; Flippen, Ruth Brooks; Arnold, Danny
  - Seventh Time Around (The) - script, 1968 Sep 3 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Shake Hands and Come Out Acting - script, 1969 Sep 6 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - She Never had the Vegas Notion - revised script, 1969 Jul 11 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - She Never Had the Vegas Notion Part I - revised script, 1969 Jul 11 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - She Never Had the Vegas Notion Part II - script, 1969 May 23 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Should All Our Old Acquaintance Be Forgot? - script, 1968 May 23 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Snow Must Go On (The) - script, 1969 May 5 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Soap Gets in Your Eyes - script, 1966 Sep 28 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Sock It To Me - script, 1968 Aug 19 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Writers: Cutler, Stan; Donovan, Martin; Arnold, Danny
  - Soot Yourself - revised script, 1970 Jun 5 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    Formerly titled Air Today Gone Tomorrow.
  - Stag Party - script, 1970 Oct 15 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Stocks and the Single Girl - script, 1969 Nov 12 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Stop the Presses, I Want to Get Off - revised script, 1970 Jul 10 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    Writers: Farr, Gordon
  - Subject Was Rabies (The) - script, 1968 Dec 13 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    Writers: Webster, Skip; Arnold, Danny
  - Sue Me, Sue Me, What Can You Do to Me? - script, 1969 Jan 14 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Super Reporter - revised script, 1970 Jun 19 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Ten Percent of Nothing is Nothing - revised script, 1969 Oct 24 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Tenor's Loving Care (A) - revised script, 1967 Jan 6 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - That Berle - revised script, 1970 Oct 2 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Writers: Walkenstein, Marvin
  - That Cake - revised script, 1970 May 8 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - That Girl's Daddy - revised script, 1970 Jul 3 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - That King - script, 1970 Oct 30 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    Writers: Murray, Warren S.
  - That Script - revised script, 1970 Aug 21 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - That Senorita - revised script, 1970 Jul 17 (Box 6, Folder 12)